Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 2538. Whittal, Yvonne: House of Mirrors. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2539. Way, Margaret: The Silver Veil. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 596)
  - Harlequin Romance 2540. Gordon, Victoria: Battle of Wills. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2541. Harvey, Samantha: Boy with Kite. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 597)
  - Harlequin Romance 2542. Neels, Betty: All Else Confusion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2543. Stratton, Rebecca: The Man from Nowhere. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 598)
  - Harlequin Romance 2543. Griffin, Jocelyn: The White Wave ("bonus free book"). (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2544. Sullivan, Jo: Suspicion. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 599)
  - Harlequin Romance 2545. Arbor, Jane: Handmaid to Midas. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2546. Lewty, Marjorie: Makeshift Marriage. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 600)
  - Harlequin Romance 2547. MacLean, Jan: All Our Tomorrows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2548. May, Wynne: Wayside Flower. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 26, Folder 601)
  - Harlequin Romance 2549. Murray, Annabel: Roots of Heaven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2550. Neels, Betty: A Dream Come True. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 602)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233513
  - Harlequin Romance 2551. Corrie, Jane: Man with Two Faces. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2552. Donnelly, Jane: Call Up the Storm. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 603)
  - Harlequin Romance 2553. Rome, Margaret: Rapture of the Deep. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2554. Scott, Alexandra: Catch a Star. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 604)
  - Harlequin Romance 2555. Steele, Jessica: Distrust Her Shadow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2556. Way, Margaret: Hunter's Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 605)
  - Harlequin Romance 2557. Mayo, Margaret: Dangerous Journey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2558. Murray, Annabel: Keegan's Kingdom. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 606)
  - Harlequin Romance 2559. Murrey, Jeneth: Tame a Proud Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2560. O'Hara, Kate: Summerhaze. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 607)
  - Harlequin Romance 2561. Rome, Margaret: Lord of the Land. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2562. Strutt, Sheila: The Flight of the Golden Hawk. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 608)
  - Harlequin Romance 2570. Dalzell, Helen: Not the Marrying Kind. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2571. George, Catherine: Dream of Midsummer. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 609)
  - Harlequin Romance 2575. Daveson, Mons: MacKenzie Country. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2579. Lewty, Marjorie: One Who Kisses. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 610)
  - Harlequin Romance 2583. Peters, Sue: Lightning Strikes Twice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2586. Westwood, Gwen: Secondhand Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 611)
  - Harlequin Romance 2599. Ayre, Jessica: Hard to Handle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2600. Dingwell, Joyce: Brother Wolf. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 612)
  - Harlequin Romance 2601. Hammond, Rosemary: Full Circle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2602. Mayo, Margaret: Return a Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 613)
  - Harlequin Romance 2603. Peake, Lilian: Night of Possession. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2604. Scott, Alexandra: Borrowed Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 614)
  - Harlequin Romance 2606. Moore, Mary: Springs of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2607. Steele, Jessica: Tomorrow - Come Soon. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 615)
  - Harlequin Romance 2608. Stevens, Lynsey: The Ashby Affair. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2609. Way, Margaret: House of Memories. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 616)
  - Harlequin Romance 2610. West, Nicola: Wildtrack. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2611. Clifford, Kay: Man of Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 617)
  - Harlequin Romance 2612. Murray, Annabel: Villa of Vengeance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2613. Pargeter, Margaret: The Silver Flame. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 618)
  - Harlequin Romance 2614. Peake, Lilian: Come Love Me. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2615. Rome, Margaret: Castle of the Lion. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 619)
  - Harlequin Romance 2616. Whittal, Yvonne: Ride the Wind. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2617. Badger, Rosemary: Corporate Lady. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 620)
  - Harlequin Romance 2619. Carson, Angela: The Face of the Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2620. Cranmer, Kathryn: Pas de Deux. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 621)
  - Harlequin Romance 2621. Henaghan, Rosalie: For Ever and a Day. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2622. Summers, Essie: A Lamp for Jonathan. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 622)
  - Harlequin Romance 2623. Flanders, Rebecca: A Modern Girl. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2624. Francis, Sara: Kate's Way. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 623)
  - Harlequin Romance 2625. Murray, Annabel: Dear Green Isle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2626. Neels, Betty: Never Too Late. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 624)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233521
  - Harlequin Romance 2627. Page, Betsy: The Bonded Heart. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2628. Parv, Valerie: Remember Me, My Love. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 625)
  - Harlequin Romance 2629. Badger, Rosemary: A Girl Called Andy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2630. Cooper, Ann: Maelstrom. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 626)
  - Harlequin Romance 2631. Gilbert, Jacqueline: The Chequered Silence. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2632. James, Dana: Desert Flower. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 627)
  - Harlequin Romance 2633. Spark, Natalie: Once More with Feeling. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2634. Way, Margaret: Almost a Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 628)
  - Harlequin Romance 2635. Donnelly, Jane: A Fierce Encounter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2638. Scott, Celia: Starfire. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 629)
  - Harlequin Romance 2639. Way, Margaret: No Alternative. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2640. West, Nicola: The Tyzak Inheritance. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 630)
  - Harlequin Romance 2641. Ayre, Jessica: New Discovery. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2642. McKeone, Dixie: Connoisseur's Choice. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 631)
  - Harlequin Romance 2643. McMahon, Barbara: Come into the Sun. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2644. Parv, Valerie: The Dreaming Dunes. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 632)
  - Harlequin Romance 2645. Summers, Essie: Season of Forgetfulness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2646. West, Nicola: Carver's Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 633)
  - Harlequin Romance 2647. Allyne, Kerry: Time to Forget. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2648. Carpenter, Amanda: A Damaged Trust. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 634)
  - Harlequin Romance 2649. Donnelly, Jane: Moon Lady. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2650. Lewty, Marjorie: Riviera Romance. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 635)
  - Harlequin Romance 2651. Peake, Lilian: A Woman in Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2652. Van der Zee, Karen: Soul Ties. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 636)
  - Harlequin Romance 2653. Armstrong, Lindsay: Don't Call It Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2654. Donnelly, Jane: The Frozen Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 637)
  - Harlequin Romance 2655. Hammond, Rosemary: Two Dozen Red Roses. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2657. Michaels, Leigh: On September Hill. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 638)
  - Harlequin Romance 2658. Way, Margaret: A Place Called Rambulara. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2659. Browning, Pamela: Touch of Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 639)
  - Harlequin Romance 2660. Charlton, Ann: A Place of Wild Honey. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2662. Lorin, Amii: Candleglow. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 640)
  - Harlequin Romance 2663. Scott, Alexandra: Storm Warning. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2664. Wibberley, Mary: Golden Haven. (Harlequin Books), 1984 (Box 28, Folder 641)
  - Harlequin Romance 2666. Neels, Betty: Once for All Time. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2667. Patterson, Morgan: Darker Fire. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 642)
  - Harlequin Romance 2668. Spenser, Emily: Chateau Villon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2669. West, Nicola: Tormented Rhapsody. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 643)
  - Harlequin Romance 2670. Young, Rena: Catch a Falling Star. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2671. Absalom, Stacy: The Passion and the Pain. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 644)
  - Harlequin Romance 2672. Day, Samantha: The Turn of the Tide. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2674. Hammond, Rosemary: The Scent of Hibiscus. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 645)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233539
  - Harlequin Romance 2675. Kirby, Rowan: Silent Stream. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2676. Marsh, Valerie: Echo of Betrayal. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 646)
  - Harlequin Romance 2677. Fowlkes, Mary: To Tame a Proud Lady. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2678. Lewty, Marjorie: Lovers' Knot. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 647)
  - Harlequin Romance 2679. McGiveny, Maura: Megan's Folly. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2680. Neels, Betty: Heidelberg Wedding. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 648)
  - Harlequin Romance 2681. Spenser, Emily: Where the Wind Blows Free. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2682. Winspear, Violet: Secret Fire. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 649)
  - Harlequin Romance 2683. Cheatham, Lillian: Island of Dolphins. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2684. Charlton, Ann: No Last Song. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 650)
  - Harlequin Romance 2685. Harris, Louise: Love's Good Fortune. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2686. Moore, Mary: Lake Haupiri Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 651)
  - Harlequin Romance 2687. Steele, Jessica: No Honourable Compromise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2688. Summers, Essie: Winter in July. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 652)
  - Harlequin Romance 2689. Absalom, Stacy: Dark Night Dawning. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2690. Gordon, Victoria: Stag at Bay. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 653)
  - Harlequin Romance 2691. Jameson, Claudia: A Time to Grow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2693. Parv, Valerie: Man and Wife. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 654)
  - Harlequin Romance 2694. Rome, Margaret: Bride by Contract. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2696. Lamb, Charlotte: Kingfisher Morning. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 655)
  - Harlequin Romance 2697. Murrey, Jeneth: The Gabrielli Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2698. Keene, Sarah: A Tender Season. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 656)
  - Harlequin Romance 2699. Strutt, Sheila: Emperor Stone. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2700. Way, Margaret: Fallen Idol. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 657)
  - Harlequin Romance 2701. Charlton, Ann: Winter Sun, Summer Rain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2702. Donnelly, Jane: Ring of Crystal. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 658)
  - Harlequin Romance 2703. Gabriel, Mary: Never Kiss a Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2704. Page, Betsy: Dark-Night Encounter. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 659)
  - Harlequin Romance 2705. Holland, Sarah: Bluebeard's Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2706. Stevens, Lynsey: Terebori's Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 660)
  - Harlequin Romance 2707. Burchell, Mary: On Wings of Song. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2708. Graham, Elizabeth: Passion's Vine. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 661)
  - Harlequin Romance 2709. Ker, Madeleine: Ice Princess. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2710. MacGregor, Miriam: Boss of Brightlands. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 662)
  - Harlequin Romance 2711. Napier, Susan: Love in the Valley. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2712. Neels, Betty: A Summer Idyll. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 663)
  - Harlequin Romance 2713. Bevan, Gloria: Southern Sunshine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2714. Gordon, Victoria: Bushranger's Mountain. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 29, Folder 664)
  - Harlequin Romance 2715. Graham, Elizabeth: Big Sur. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2716. Ker, Madeleine: Hostage. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 665)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233547
  - Harlequin Romance 2717. Murray, Annabel: The Cotswold Lion. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2718. West, Nicola: A Rooted Sorrow. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 666)
  - Harlequin Romance 2719. Cranmer, Kathryn: Wrecker's Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2720. George, Catherine: Desirable Property. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 667)
  - Harlequin Romance 2721. McAllister, Anne: Dare to Trust. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2722. McKeone, Dixie: The Matchmaking Department. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 668)
  - Harlequin Romance 2723. Napier, Susan: Sweet Vixen. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2724. Way, Margaret: Eagle's Ridge. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 669)
  - Harlequin Romance 2725. Allyne, Kerry: Merringannee Bluff. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2726. Campbell, Bethany: After the Stars Fall. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 670)
  - Harlequin Romance 2728. Murrey, Jeneth: Return to Arkady. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2729. Neels, Betty: At the End of the Day. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 671)
  - Harlequin Romance 2730. Page, Betsy: The Wyomian. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2731. Conrad, Helen: Tears of Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 672)
  - Harlequin Romance 2732. Gregor, Carol: Lord of the Air. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2733. MacGregor, Miriam: Spring at Sevenoaks. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 673)
  - Harlequin Romance 2734. Michaels, Leigh: Wednesday's Child. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2735. Scott, Celia: Where the Gods Dwell. (Harlequin Books), 1985 (Box 30, Folder 674)
  - Harlequin Romance 2736. Westwood, Gwen: Wilderness Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2737. Allyne, Kerry: Return to Wallaby Creek. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 675)
  - Harlequin Romance 2738. Donnelly, Jane: To Cage a Whirlwind. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2739. Goldrick, Emma: The Trouble with Bridges. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 676)
  - Harlequin Romance 2740. Keene, Sarah: Air of Enchantment. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2742. Whittal, Yvonne: Wild Jasmine. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 677)
  - Harlequin Romance 2743. Corrie, Jane: Cartier's Strike. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2744. Hughes, Tracy: Quiet Lightning. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 678)
  - Harlequin Romance 2745. Lane, Roumelia: Night of the Beguine. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2746. Lewty, Marjorie: A Lake in Kyoto. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 679)
  - Harlequin Romance 2747. MacLeod, Jean S.: Valley of the Snows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2748. Michaels, Leigh: Come Next Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 680)
  - Harlequin Romance 2750. Forsythe, Melissa: The Perfect Choice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2751. Henaghan, Rosalie: Safe Harbour. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 681)
  - Harlequin Romance 2753. Shore, Edwina: A Will to Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2754. Strutt, Sheila: He Was the Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 682)
  - Harlequin Romance 2761. Allyne, Kerry: Stranger in Town. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2763. Fox, Susan: Vows of the Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 683)
  - Harlequin Romance 2764. Harvey, Samantha: Amaryllis Dreaming. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2765. Parv, Valerie: Ask Me No Questions. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 30, Folder 684)
  - Harlequin Romance 2766. Summers, Essie: To Bring You Joy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2767. Cranmer, Kahtryn: Secret Lover. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 685)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233554
  - Harlequin Romance 2768. Macomber, Debbie: The Matchmakers. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2769. Scott, Alexandra: Wildfire. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 686)
  - Harlequin Romance 2770. Warren, Betsy: Song Without Words. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2771. West, Nicola: Comeback. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 687)
  - Harlequin Romance 2772. Wilder, Quinn: That Man from Texas. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2773. Badger, Rosemary: Shadows of Eden. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 688)
  - Harlequin Romance 2774. Dominique, Meg: Sand Castles. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2775. Gordon, Victoria: Age of Consent. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 689)
  - Harlequin Romance 2776. Kirby, Rowan: Power Point. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2777. McMahon, Barbara: Bluebells on the Hill. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 690)
  - Harlequin Romance 2778. Parv, Valerie: Return to Faraway. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2779. Campbell, Bethany: Only a Woman. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 691)
  - Harlequin Romance 2780. Clark, Sandra: A Fool to Say Yes. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2781. McGiveny, Maura: The Right Time. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 692)
  - Harlequin Romance 2782. Murray, Anabel: The Plumed Serpent. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2783. Walker, Kate: Game of Hazard. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 693)
  - Harlequin Romance 2784. Way, Margaret: The Tiger's Cage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2785. Armstrong, Lindsay: Some Say Love. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 694)
  - Harlequin Romance 2786. Kirk, Mariel: Prisoner of Shadow Mountain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2787. Neels, Betty: A Girl Named Rose. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 695)
  - Harlequin Romance 2789. Steele, Jessica: Misleading Encounter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2790. Wells, Angela: Sweet Poison. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 696)
  - Harlequin Romance 2791. Edwards, Emily Ruth: Hunter's Snare. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2792. Hughes, Tracy: Impressions. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 697)
  - Harlequin Romance 2793. Jantz, Caroline: Separate Lives. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2794. MacGregor, Miriam: Call of the Mountain. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 698)
  - Harlequin Romance 2795. Mayo, Margaret: Impulsive Challenge. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2796. Westwood, Gwen: Safari Heartbreak. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 699)
  - Harlequin Romance 2797. Parv, Valerie: Boss of Yarrakina. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2798. Shore, Edwina: The Last Barrier. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 700)
  - Harlequin Romance 2799. Spark, Natalie: One Life at a Time. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2800. Steele, Jessica: So Near, So Far. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 701)
  - Harlequin Romance 2801. Summers, Essie: Autumn in April. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2802. Thompson, Marcella: Breaking Free. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 702)
  - Harlequin Romance 2804. Lamb, Charlotte: The Heron Quest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2806. Michaels, Leigh: Capture a Shadow. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 703)
  - Harlequin Romance 2807. Murrey, Jeneth: The Waiting Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2808. Neels, Betty: Two Weeks to Remember. (Harlequin Books), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 704)
  - Harlequin Romance 2812. Peters, Sue: Never Touch a Tiger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2814. Wood, Sara: Perfumes of Arabia. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 705)
  - Harlequin Romance 2816. Carter, Rosemary: Walk into Tomorrow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2817. Hammond, Rosemary: Plain Jane. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 706)
  - Harlequin Romance 2818. Manning, Liza: The Glass Madonna. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2819. Murray, Annabel: Wild for to Hold. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 707)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233562
  - Harlequin Romance 2820. Way, Margaret: Innocent in Eden. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2821. Arthur, Katherine: Road to Love. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 708)
  - Harlequin Romance 2823. MacGregor, Miriam: Winter at Whitecliffs. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2825. Power, Elizabeth: Rude Awakening. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 709)
  - Harlequin Romance 2826. Walker, Kate: Rough Diamond. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2827. Badger, Rosemary: Time to Trust. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 710)
  - Harlequin Romance 2828. Keene, Sarah: Earthly Treasures. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2829. Kirby, Rowan: Contrasts. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 711)
  - Harlequin Romance 2830. Michaels, Leigh: O'Hara's Legacy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2832. Way, Margaret: Diamond Valley. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 712)
  - Harlequin Romance 2833. Duke, Elizabeth: Softly Flits a Shadow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2834. Lane, Roumelia: Tempest in the Tropics. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 713)
  - Harlequin Romance 2835. Macomber, Debbie: Love by Degree. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2837. MacLeod, Jean S.: The Apollo Man. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 714)
  - Harlequin Romance 2838. McKeone, Dixie: The Harlequin Hero. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2840. Day, Samantha: For Karin's Sake. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 715)
  - Harlequin Romance 2841. James, Dana: The Marati Legacy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2842. Jameson, Claudia: Immune to Love. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 716)
  - Harlequin Romance 2843. Murray, Annabel: Ring of Claddagh. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2844. Wells, Angela: Moroccan Madness. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 717)
  - Harlequin Romance 2845. Allan, Jeanne: When Love Flies By. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2847. Kirby, Rowan: Fusion. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 718)
  - Harlequin Romance 2848. Lewty, Marjorie: In Love with the Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2849. MacGregor, Miriam: Stairway to Destiny. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 719)
  - Harlequin Romance 2850. Steele, Jessica: Beyond Her Control. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2856. Wilson, Patricia: Bride of Diaz. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 720)
  - Harlequin Romance 2857. Jameson, Claudia: A Man of Contrasts. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2859. Nickson, Hilda: Voyage of Discovery. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 721)
  - Harlequin Romance 2860. Parv, Valerie: The Love Artist. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2865. Hamilton, Diana: Impulsive Attraction. (Harlequin Books), 1987 (Box 32, Folder 722)